{"doc_id": "doc-0001", "text": "Barack Obama was born in Hawaii. Obama later moved to Chicago, where he worked for the City Council.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 12}, {"start": 7, "end": 12}, {"start": 64, "end": 66}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 25, "end": 31}, {"start": 54, "end": 61}]}, {"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 87, "end": 99}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0002", "text": "Alice met Bob in Paris on Monday, then Alice flew home.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0003", "text": "She joined the Bank of America board in 2010 before leaving America.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 30}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 23, "end": 30}, {"start": 60, "end": 67}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 40, "end": 44}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0004", "text": "🚀 Elon flew to Berlin 😀 with SpaceX in March.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 2, "end": 6}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 21}]}, {"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 39, "end": 44}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0005", "text": "Annie and George Washington visited Mount Vernon.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"fragments": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}, {"start": 17, "end": 27}]}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 10, "end": 27}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 36, "end": 48}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0007", "text": "Just saw Taylor Swift live in London last night, incredible show!", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0008", "text": "Great thread — Ahmed explained the whole thing better than the news did.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 20}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0009", "text": "Nobody expected the announcement to arrive so early in the year.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0010", "text": "The mayor of London opened the bridge on Sunday morning.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0011", "text": "Nobody expected the announcement to arrive so early in the year.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0012", "text": "The United Nations convened in Geneva to discuss the treaty.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 4, "end": 18}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 31, "end": 37}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0013", "text": "Reporters from Reuters interviewed Lionel Messi in Miami.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 35, "end": 47}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 51, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0014", "text": "Microsoft acquired the startup founded by Priya Sharma in Bangalore.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 9}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 42, "end": 54}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 58, "end": 67}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0015", "text": "The mayor of London opened the bridge on Sunday morning.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0016", "text": "She flew from Tel Aviv to Berlin and met Hannah at the airport.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 14, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 26, "end": 32}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 47}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0017", "text": "Analysts at Goldman Sachs revised their forecast for 2027.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 12, "end": 25}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 53, "end": 57}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0018", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0019", "text": "Serena Williams announced her retirement in New York yesterday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 15}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 44, "end": 52}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0020", "text": "Reporters from Reuters interviewed Lionel Messi in Miami.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 35, "end": 47}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 51, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0021", "text": "Nobody expected the announcement to arrive so early in the year.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0022", "text": "She flew from Tel Aviv to Berlin and met Hannah at the airport.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 14, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 26, "end": 32}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 47}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0023", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0024", "text": "Analysts at Goldman Sachs revised their forecast for 2027.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 12, "end": 25}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 53, "end": 57}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0025", "text": "Marie Curie studied in Paris before returning to Warsaw.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 11}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 23, "end": 28}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 55}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0026", "text": "She flew from Tel Aviv to Berlin and met Hannah at the airport.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 14, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 26, "end": 32}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 47}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0027", "text": "The committee will publish its findings next month.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0028", "text": "She flew from Tel Aviv to Berlin and met Hannah at the airport.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 14, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 26, "end": 32}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 47}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0029", "text": "Reporters from Reuters interviewed Lionel Messi in Miami.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 35, "end": 47}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 51, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0030", "text": "Analysts at Goldman Sachs revised their forecast for 2027.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 12, "end": 25}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 53, "end": 57}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0031", "text": "Great thread — Ahmed explained the whole thing better than the news did.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 20}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0032", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0033", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0034", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0035", "text": "Watching the storm roll into Boston right now, stay safe everyone.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0036", "text": "Analysts at Goldman Sachs revised their forecast for 2027.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 12, "end": 25}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 53, "end": 57}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0037", "text": "Microsoft acquired the startup founded by Priya Sharma in Bangalore.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 9}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 42, "end": 54}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 58, "end": 67}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0038", "text": "Toyota and Honda both reported record sales in Japan this quarter.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 6}]}, {"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 11, "end": 16}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 47, "end": 52}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0039", "text": "The mayor of London opened the bridge on Sunday morning.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0040", "text": "Great thread — Ahmed explained the whole thing better than the news did.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 20}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0041", "text": "The United Nations convened in Geneva to discuss the treaty.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 4, "end": 18}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 31, "end": 37}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0042", "text": "Nobody expected the announcement to arrive so early in the year.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0043", "text": "She flew from Tel Aviv to Berlin and met Hannah at the airport.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 14, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 26, "end": 32}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 47}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0044", "text": "The mayor of London opened the bridge on Sunday morning.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0045", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0046", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0047", "text": "The mayor of London opened the bridge on Sunday morning.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0048", "text": "She flew from Tel Aviv to Berlin and met Hannah at the airport.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 14, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 26, "end": 32}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 47}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0049", "text": "Serena Williams announced her retirement in New York yesterday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 15}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 44, "end": 52}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0050", "text": "Nobody expected the announcement to arrive so early in the year.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0051", "text": "Watching the storm roll into Boston right now, stay safe everyone.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0052", "text": "The committee will publish its findings next month.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0053", "text": "Toyota and Honda both reported record sales in Japan this quarter.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 6}]}, {"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 11, "end": 16}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 47, "end": 52}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0054", "text": "Microsoft acquired the startup founded by Priya Sharma in Bangalore.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 9}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 42, "end": 54}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 58, "end": 67}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0055", "text": "Nobody expected the announcement to arrive so early in the year.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0056", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0057", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0058", "text": "Microsoft acquired the startup founded by Priya Sharma in Bangalore.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 9}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 42, "end": 54}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 58, "end": 67}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0059", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0060", "text": "Marie Curie studied in Paris before returning to Warsaw.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 11}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 23, "end": 28}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 55}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0061", "text": "Great thread — Ahmed explained the whole thing better than the news did.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 20}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0062", "text": "Marie Curie studied in Paris before returning to Warsaw.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 11}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 23, "end": 28}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 55}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0063", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0064", "text": "Great thread — Ahmed explained the whole thing better than the news did.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 20}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0065", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0066", "text": "The United Nations convened in Geneva to discuss the treaty.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 4, "end": 18}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 31, "end": 37}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0067", "text": "The United Nations convened in Geneva to discuss the treaty.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 4, "end": 18}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 31, "end": 37}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0068", "text": "Watching the storm roll into Boston right now, stay safe everyone.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0069", "text": "The mayor of London opened the bridge on Sunday morning.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0070", "text": "The committee will publish its findings next month.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0071", "text": "Marie Curie studied in Paris before returning to Warsaw.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 11}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 23, "end": 28}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 55}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0072", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0073", "text": "Analysts at Goldman Sachs revised their forecast for 2027.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 12, "end": 25}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 53, "end": 57}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0074", "text": "The United Nations convened in Geneva to discuss the treaty.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 4, "end": 18}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 31, "end": 37}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0075", "text": "Microsoft acquired the startup founded by Priya Sharma in Bangalore.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 9}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 42, "end": 54}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 58, "end": 67}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0076", "text": "She flew from Tel Aviv to Berlin and met Hannah at the airport.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 14, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 26, "end": 32}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 47}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0077", "text": "Serena Williams announced her retirement in New York yesterday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 15}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 44, "end": 52}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0078", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0079", "text": "Serena Williams announced her retirement in New York yesterday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 15}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 44, "end": 52}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0080", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0081", "text": "Marie Curie studied in Paris before returning to Warsaw.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 11}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 23, "end": 28}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 55}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0082", "text": "Reporters from Reuters interviewed Lionel Messi in Miami.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 35, "end": 47}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 51, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0083", "text": "The committee will publish its findings next month.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0084", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0085", "text": "The mayor of London opened the bridge on Sunday morning.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0086", "text": "Reporters from Reuters interviewed Lionel Messi in Miami.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 35, "end": 47}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 51, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0087", "text": "She flew from Tel Aviv to Berlin and met Hannah at the airport.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 14, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 26, "end": 32}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 47}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0088", "text": "The United Nations convened in Geneva to discuss the treaty.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 4, "end": 18}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 31, "end": 37}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0089", "text": "The mayor of London opened the bridge on Sunday morning.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0090", "text": "Nobody expected the announcement to arrive so early in the year.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0091", "text": "The committee will publish its findings next month.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0092", "text": "Marie Curie studied in Paris before returning to Warsaw.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 11}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 23, "end": 28}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 55}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0093", "text": "Marie Curie studied in Paris before returning to Warsaw.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 11}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 23, "end": 28}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 55}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0094", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0095", "text": "Marie Curie studied in Paris before returning to Warsaw.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 11}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 23, "end": 28}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 55}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0096", "text": "Marie Curie studied in Paris before returning to Warsaw.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 11}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 23, "end": 28}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 55}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0097", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0098", "text": "Great thread — Ahmed explained the whole thing better than the news did.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 20}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0099", "text": "Microsoft acquired the startup founded by Priya Sharma in Bangalore.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 9}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 42, "end": 54}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 58, "end": 67}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0100", "text": "Serena Williams announced her retirement in New York yesterday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 15}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 44, "end": 52}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0101", "text": "Watching the storm roll into Boston right now, stay safe everyone.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0102", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0103", "text": "Reporters from Reuters interviewed Lionel Messi in Miami.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 35, "end": 47}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 51, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0104", "text": "Great thread — Ahmed explained the whole thing better than the news did.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 20}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0105", "text": "Analysts at Goldman Sachs revised their forecast for 2027.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 12, "end": 25}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 53, "end": 57}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0106", "text": "Analysts at Goldman Sachs revised their forecast for 2027.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 12, "end": 25}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 53, "end": 57}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0107", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0108", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0109", "text": "Reporters from Reuters interviewed Lionel Messi in Miami.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 35, "end": 47}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 51, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0110", "text": "The mayor of London opened the bridge on Sunday morning.", "entities": []}
{"doc_id": "doc-0111", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0112", "text": "Microsoft acquired the startup founded by Priya Sharma in Bangalore.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 9}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 42, "end": 54}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 58, "end": 67}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0113", "text": "Toyota and Honda both reported record sales in Japan this quarter.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 6}]}, {"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 11, "end": 16}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 47, "end": 52}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0114", "text": "Great thread — Ahmed explained the whole thing better than the news did.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 20}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0115", "text": "Serena Williams announced her retirement in New York yesterday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 15}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 44, "end": 52}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0116", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0117", "text": "Apple opened a new campus in Austin last April.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 5}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 29, "end": 35}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 46}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0118", "text": "The United Nations convened in Geneva to discuss the treaty.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 4, "end": 18}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 31, "end": 37}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0119", "text": "She flew from Tel Aviv to Berlin and met Hannah at the airport.", "entities": [{"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 14, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 26, "end": 32}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 41, "end": 47}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0120", "text": "The United Nations convened in Geneva to discuss the treaty.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 4, "end": 18}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 31, "end": 37}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0121", "text": "Angela Merkel met Emmanuel Macron in Brussels on Tuesday.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 13}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 18, "end": 33}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 37, "end": 45}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 49, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0122", "text": "Toyota and Honda both reported record sales in Japan this quarter.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 6}]}, {"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 11, "end": 16}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 47, "end": 52}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0123", "text": "Toyota and Honda both reported record sales in Japan this quarter.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 0, "end": 6}]}, {"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 11, "end": 16}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 47, "end": 52}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0124", "text": "Analysts at Goldman Sachs revised their forecast for 2027.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 12, "end": 25}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 53, "end": 57}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0125", "text": "Reporters from Reuters interviewed Lionel Messi in Miami.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 22}]}, {"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 35, "end": 47}]}, {"type": "LOC", "mentions": [{"start": 51, "end": 56}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0126", "text": "Analysts at Goldman Sachs revised their forecast for 2027.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 12, "end": 25}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 53, "end": 57}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0127", "text": "Great thread — Ahmed explained the whole thing better than the news did.", "entities": [{"type": "PER", "mentions": [{"start": 15, "end": 20}]}]}
{"doc_id": "doc-0128", "text": "Analysts at Goldman Sachs revised their forecast for 2027.", "entities": [{"type": "ORG", "mentions": [{"start": 12, "end": 25}]}, {"type": "TIME", "mentions": [{"start": 53, "end": 57}]}]}
